filedroid.net 2013-05-07

# Privacy Policy | filedroid

We are committed to protecting the privacy of the personally identifiable information that we collect from you as you use this website according to this Privacy Policy. By submitting information on the website, you agree to our use of such information as described herein.

Type of use: When you visit our website, you do not have to register to browse our site. If you decide to become a member and use our services ("activate filedroid"), you will be required to register to enable both parties to fulfill the contract. Please see our General Terms of Business & Conditions for Use for further details. To submit a valid registration you have to submit the data the respective form fields, e.g. full name, address, e-mail, telephone number and payment data.

We rely on widely accepted standards of information security in order to protect your personally identifiable data from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. If you submit data to us via our website, the transmission is secured with SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology.

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your permission, except if it is necessary to fulfill the service or on grounds of the contractual relationship you have with us, e.g. to enable the processing of payments in cooperation with payment service providers or for marketing purposes.

We shall also be authorized to disclose your personal information as required or permitted by applicable laws, rules or regulations, or in response to legal inquiries arising from information you have provided to us.

By using this website, you consent to the collection, use and storage of your information by us in the manner described in this privacy policy. After the end of a membership your personally identifiable information remains stored within the legally required period and subsequently will be deleted. If you just want to unsubscribe from our newsletter, you may use the respective "unsubscribe" hyperlink in each newsletter. If you want to revoke your agreement with our usage of your personally identifiable information, please contact us through our support form. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time.

Contact Legal notice
